{
    "subject": "Tonia_Marketaki",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Crystal_Nights",
    "human_readable": "Tonia Marketaki directed Crystal Nights.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7506580352783203,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Crystal Nights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.738755464553833,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Tonia Marketaki."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6972085237503052,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie directed by Tonia Marketaki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6083987355232239,
            "question": "Are there any other movies directed by Tonia Marketaki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.506783664226532,
            "question": "Who are the actors in Crystal Nights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48619869351387024,
            "question": "Is Crystal Nights a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4168955981731415,
            "question": "What year was Crystal Nights released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3397504985332489,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Tonia Marketaki's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3367213308811188,
            "question": "What genre is Crystal Nights likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3279312551021576,
            "question": "Where can I watch Crystal Nights?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tonia Marketaki directed Crystal Nights.",
            "html": "yago_18076_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Crystal Nights likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_18076_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Tonia Marketaki's work?",
            "html": "yago_18076_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Crystal Nights released?",
            "html": "yago_18076_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18076_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Tonia Marketaki directed Crystal Nights.\" The details mention her as a film director and describe \"Crystal Nights\" as one of her films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}